[{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664330024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":22555,"timeElapsed":116514},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664349746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":19717,"timeElapsed":136237},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664356393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":6642,"timeElapsed":142884},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664364417,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8019,"timeElapsed":150908},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664373064,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":8644,"timeElapsed":159555},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664378652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":5584,"timeElapsed":165143},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664382238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3582,"timeElapsed":168728},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664387945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":5703,"timeElapsed":174435},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664391775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"232","question":"Are there any vegetables you don’t eat? When was the last time you ate one of those things?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3827,"timeElapsed":178266},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664426068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5453,"timeElapsed":212559},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664431035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4962,"timeElapsed":217526},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664435817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":4774,"timeElapsed":222308},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664439076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3255,"timeElapsed":225567},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664442218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3138,"timeElapsed":228708},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664445535,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3314,"timeElapsed":232026},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664451360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5821,"timeElapsed":237850},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664458828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":7464,"timeElapsed":245318},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664461688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2857,"timeElapsed":248179},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664470195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2608,"timeElapsed":256686},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664472869,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2672,"timeElapsed":259360},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664475331,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2457,"timeElapsed":261821},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664478514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3181,"timeElapsed":265005},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664480698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2181,"timeElapsed":267189},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664485415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4710,"timeElapsed":271906},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664488283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2861,"timeElapsed":274773},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664492083,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3797,"timeElapsed":278574},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664495441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3353,"timeElapsed":281931},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664498442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"173","question":"What is the weirdest thing you have ever found in your pocket after doing laundry?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2998,"timeElapsed":284933},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664504501,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2585,"timeElapsed":290992},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664507195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2691,"timeElapsed":293686},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664511137,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3939,"timeElapsed":297628},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664514072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2931,"timeElapsed":300563},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664518148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":4073,"timeElapsed":304639},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664520719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2567,"timeElapsed":307210},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664524077,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3354,"timeElapsed":310568},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664527286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3204,"timeElapsed":313776},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664530812,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"216","question":"Do you have a bedtime routine? What do you typically do to fall asleep?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3523,"timeElapsed":317303},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664537667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3719,"timeElapsed":324157},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664546197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":8508,"timeElapsed":332688},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664549920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3720,"timeElapsed":336410},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664552200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2271,"timeElapsed":338689},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664555586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3376,"timeElapsed":342077},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664558277,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":2682,"timeElapsed":344767},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664562549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4261,"timeElapsed":349040},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664566148,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3594,"timeElapsed":352639},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664568703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2552,"timeElapsed":355194},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664571070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"18","question":"What is your most terrible memory?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2363,"timeElapsed":357560},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664577118,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3591,"timeElapsed":363608},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664583192,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6071,"timeElapsed":369683},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664585815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":2620,"timeElapsed":372306},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664588522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2701,"timeElapsed":375011},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664591066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2540,"timeElapsed":377557},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664593335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2262,"timeElapsed":379825},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664596213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2859,"timeElapsed":382703},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664599024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2802,"timeElapsed":385515},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664601451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"111","question":"What would your past self think of your current self? Would you say a lot has changed regarding how you think about the world and what you believe in?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":2422,"timeElapsed":387941},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664607558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4082,"timeElapsed":394049},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664610198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2636,"timeElapsed":396689},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664612606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2404,"timeElapsed":399097},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664615288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2676,"timeElapsed":401779},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664618441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2930,"timeElapsed":404932},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664621585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3136,"timeElapsed":408076},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664624693,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3105,"timeElapsed":411184},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664626749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2053,"timeElapsed":413240},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664629058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"65","question":"What seemingly ordinary moment in your life turned out to be a major turning point?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2305,"timeElapsed":415549},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664635659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":2451,"timeElapsed":422149},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664639338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3674,"timeElapsed":425829},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664641397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2052,"timeElapsed":427888},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664644302,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2899,"timeElapsed":430793},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664646828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2513,"timeElapsed":433316},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664648963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2121,"timeElapsed":435454},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664652633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3661,"timeElapsed":439124},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664655353,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2702,"timeElapsed":441844},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664658094,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2728,"timeElapsed":444585},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664663481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2899,"timeElapsed":449972},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664667261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3775,"timeElapsed":453752},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664669411,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2144,"timeElapsed":455901},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664672329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2913,"timeElapsed":458820},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664674289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1953,"timeElapsed":460779},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664676655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2360,"timeElapsed":463146},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664679016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2356,"timeElapsed":465507},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664681149,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2129,"timeElapsed":467640},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664683472,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"68","question":"What is a holiday tradition that your family valued?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2321,"timeElapsed":469963},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664689116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3308,"timeElapsed":475606},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664692916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3796,"timeElapsed":479406},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664696251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3331,"timeElapsed":482742},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664700902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4646,"timeElapsed":487393},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664704112,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3206,"timeElapsed":490603},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664707404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3289,"timeElapsed":493895},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664709938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2530,"timeElapsed":496429},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664714706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4763,"timeElapsed":501197},{"subjectID":"4srmj1j1ka","prolificID":"67149550efaf4aeb47c5d662","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677422000d3e7054de963b2e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664717487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2777,"timeElapsed":503977}]